（画外音）我们来探索
控制台的另一个部分
目前为止 你发送的所有消息
messages that you've sent
have been sent to everybody 都发送到了使用该应用的每一个人
that's using the app.
That's because we used 这是因为我们使用了这个“用户组”(user segment)目标
this user segment target.
But what if I want to 但是如果我想将通知发送到
send a notification
to a specific user? 一名特定用户呢？
In the console, I could 在控制台中 我可以选择“单个设备”(single device)
select single device.
But now it's asking me for 但现在 它要我提供一个叫作 FCM 注册令牌
something called an FCM
registration token.的东西
An FCM registration    FCM 注册令牌是一个由数字和字符
token is a string
of numbers and 组成的字符串 用于
characters that is used
to uniquely identify a device.唯一地标识设备
It's generated when the app  它在应用首次启动时生成
first starts and changes,
say, if you uninstall 并在你卸载和重装应用后更改
and reinstall the app.
The FCM server can use these    FCM 服务器可以使用这些独特的令牌将消息
unique tokens to send messages
to specific devices. 发送到特定设备
So let's see how you 那么来看看你如何找到
actually find out
what the FCM registration 自己设备的 FCM 注册令牌
token is for your device.
There's actually pretty 实际上网上有比较清楚的
clear online documentation
about how to do this.方法文档
If I scroll down,我向下滚动 第一步是
the first step is
to create a service that extends 创建一个扩展 FirebaseInstanceIDService
from Firebase instance ID
service. 的服务
Like all Android 像所有 Android 组件一样 该服务
components, the service
needs to be registered 需要注册到清单文件
to the manifest.
Now, to be able to catch the 现在 要在为你的设备生成令牌时
event when a token is generated
for your device, it's 捕获事件 你需要
important that you
have this intent filter here.在此添加 intent 过滤器
它具有操作 Instance_ID_Event
And after extending this service 在扩展此服务并将它添加到清单文件后
and adding it to the manifest,
the only other real 另一件你真正需要做的事
thing that you need to do
is implement this on 是实现此 onTokenRefresh 方法
token refresh method.
And this method is part of the 而此方法是 FirebaseInstanceIDService 的
Firebase instance ID service
class.一部分
Functionally, you could do 从功能方面来说 在调用此方法时 你可以
a couple of different things
when this method is called.执行多个不同的操作
But for you, you just want 但是对于你 则只需知道这个令牌的内容
to know what that token is,
so you can actually 以便在日志中将它实际打印出来
print it out in a log.
For my Firebase instance 对于我的 FirebaseInstanceIDService 类
ID service class,
I made a new folder called 我创建了一个叫作 FCM 的新文件夹并将它保存在了里面
FCM and saved it there.
In this class, I simply have an 在这个类中 我有一个 onTokenRefresh 方法
on token refresh method, which
then prints out the token. 它会将令牌打印出来
I then also have a 还有一个无用的 sendRegistrationToSever
useless send registration
to server method, which 方法 在此课程中我不会
I won't be doing anything
with in this lesson.用到它
But you can read the comments to 但你可以阅读注释 了解它的用处
see what it would be used for.
I'm going to go 接下来我要运行我的应用
ahead and run my app.
And then here in the 然后在这里的日志中 可以看到
logs, I can see that I've
generated an instance ID token. 产生了一个实例 ID 令牌
OK, so I'm going 那么我复制此令牌
to copy this token.
And then I'm going to paste 并将它粘贴在控制台中的这个位置
it here in the console.
I'll enter some 我要输入一些消息文本 然后
message text, and I'll
go ahead and send the message. 发送消息
And we can see that I 可以看到我收到了这条消息
just got this message.
OK, now you can 好的 现在你可以自己操作了
do this yourself.
Go ahead and generate the unique 使用 FirebaseInstanceIDService
token for your device using
a Firebase instance 为你的设备生成唯一的令牌
ID service class.
Print that token 在日志中打印出此令牌
out to the logs,
and then use it to send an FCM 然后使用它向你自己的设备发送 FCM 消息
message just to your device.
When you're done, enter 完成后 作为下一个小测试的一部分
the FCM registration token
as part of the next quiz. 输入此 FCM 注册令牌